Anybody here drive for Uber?
Oh, nobody like to say that, huh?
>> [laughter]
>> I read somewhere one out of every nine
people in America drive for Uber or
Lyft. You know what that means? 19 of
you [\h__\h] are lying. That's what that
means.
Ain't nothing wrong with driving for
Uber or Lyft. Ain't nothing wrong with
it. A lot of people do it. Some people I
know some people who do it to make a
little extra money. I know some people
who do just that and they do fine out of
life. Then you got those people who
drive for Uber or Lyft and and they do
it because they love people.
And those folks can go directly to hell.
You understand?
>> [laughter]
>> Don't you say [\h__\h] to me when I get in
your car.
The greatest invention they came up with
is the don't talk to me button.
There's a button on the app that you can
press that instructs the driver to shut
the [\h__\h] up and drop me off.
I hit that every time.
>> [laughter]
>> I don't like Ubers, man. I really don't.
I'm just getting used to them now. The
main reason I don't like them is cuz
there are there's no real security. What
they do is they just send you a picture
of the person and they send you his face
and their first name and the kind of car
they're in and that's it. So now when
they pull up to the curb, I got to look
like a prostitute trying to figure out
if this the [\h__\h] in the car or not.
>> [laughter]
[laughter]
>> Steve?
I say his name, he say my name. I go
ahead and trust this [\h__\h] with
my life. That's it.
>> [laughter]
>> I had somebody pick me up one day. He
wasn't the dude that was on the app. You
ever had that happen to you?
This [\h__\h] pulled up. It was
supposed to be a dude named Elliot in a
black Honda Accord. It was a white dude,
little circle glasses and red hair.
Looked like a [\h__\h] Elliot. Here come
the Honda Accord pull up. I looked in
there do my little whole stroll.
>> [laughter]
>> I looked in there there was a Hispanic
gentleman in there.
Big white t-shirt, gold chain, [\h__\h]
neck tattoo, couple on his face.
I was like, "Hmm.
Elliot?"
>> [laughter]
>> He's like, "Get in, fool."
I was like, "Nah, man. Go ahead, bro.
I'm good."
>> [laughter]
>> I'm going to go ahead and cancel that
one. I ain't [\h__\h] with you.
I waited
I waited until he pulled off. I was
like, "WHAT YOU DO TO ELLIOT?"
>> [laughter]
>> THAT WAS PROBABLY ELLIOT'S last ride.
He's like, "And give me your phone, too,
[\h__\h]
I'm going to steal your job."
>> [laughter]
>> I ain't know you can get kicked out of
an Uber.
That [\h__\h] happened to me.
It didn't happen cuz I was doing nothing
crazy. It happened cuz I'm grown. And
when I say I'm grown, that just means
I'm to the age where I'm not working on
myself no more.
>> [laughter]
>> My flaws are my flaws. Either you [\h__\h]
with me or you don't at this point.
I ain't talking about nothing major. I'm
just talking about regular [\h__\h] Like,
you know, like I'm grumpy in the morning
before I get my coffee. Like if I don't
Hey, man. Don't don't come at me crazy
before I get my coffee. You might catch
a stray. You know what I'm saying?
And that's important to the story. I was
doing this show in Tennessee. I had a
red eye flight to get there. I didn't
get no sleep on the plane. And I got the
most talkative driver in the world when
this [\h__\h] picked me up. I don't
know if he just powered through my
little don't talk to me button or what.
I gave him every sign that I did not
want to talk. I had a big headphones on.
I had my hoodie up. And I was looking
out the side window. I was looking so
far out the side window I I my thigh on
the back seat. [\h__\h] I was
giving this [\h__\h] no energy at all.
He powered through all of that. So,
WHERE DID YOU FLY IN FROM?
>> [laughter]
>> THIS [\h__\h] I WAS LIKE, "Los
Angeles." Oh, I love Los Angeles. Me and
my sister used to go to Los Angeles
every summer. My parents would rent a RV
and we'd go down to Disney and after
Disney the next day we'd go to SeaWorld
and sometimes if we're lucky we go all
the way up the coast and head back up to
the Bay Area. It's fun up there. Sure
does get cold. You ever been up there?
If you've been up there before you need
a jacket at night [laughter] time.
I'm like, "Shut [applause] the [\h__\h] up."
He turned into a tour guide. You ever
had one turn into a tour guide on you?
And I'm not talking about historical
facts. I'm talking random [\h__\h] in the
neighborhood.
He was like, "We about to pull up on one
of the greatest Targets on the East
Coast."
>> [laughter]
>> This thing's like a baby Bloomingdale's.
It's great.
Here's where I lost it and got in
trouble. We pulled up to this stop sign
and he didn't he didn't go nowhere. He
just sat there.
And I don't know about y'all, but when
I'm not driving the inside of my body is
still driving.
When you hit the brakes, [\h__\h] we hit
the brakes. [\h__\h] I'm in there with
you.
And I'm sitting at this stop sign like,
"Ain't this a [\h__\h] Ain't nobody even
around. What the [\h__\h] is really going
on?" Made the mistake of making eye
contact with him in the rearview. He was
like, "Glad I got your attention."
>> [laughter]
>> You see that second house over there on
the left?
That's where my sister lives.
I snapped. I was like, "Bro, I don't
give a [\h__\h] about you, your sister,
nobody else. Shut the [\h__\h] up and drop
me off. [\h__\h] that is enough."
>> [laughter]
>> It got all quiet in the car.
Then my phone went off. Boom.
It's like, "Your ride has been ended." I
was like, "Ain't [laughter] this a
bitch?"
So, you ain't even want to talk about
this, you old [\h__\h] ass [\h__\h] I see
that, huh?
He drive
>> [laughter]
>> I felt all bad at first. You ever curse
somebody out and feel bad like you
snapped on somebody at work?
Somebody up did some [\h__\h] to your food
or something. You had to walk out and
let everybody have it.
>> [laughter]
>> You know.
Then you be looking for advocates in the
in the street something.
WHICH ONE OF YOU [\h__\h] TOUCHED
MY SANDWICH? I'LL BEAT SOME ASS IN THIS
[\h__\h]
THEY DRANK MY JUICE.
>> [laughter]
>> I'M UP HERE feeling bad. This [\h__\h]
kicked me out.
He dropped me off at that Target he was
telling me about.
Had me looking crazy as hell, man. I'm
walking around with my carry-on bags,
flip flops, two hats on. [\h__\h] I look
crazy as [\h__\h] Look like I'm about to
shoplift immediately.
He wasn't bullshitting though. It was a
beautiful Target. That [\h__\h] was
crazy.
Had a Starbucks in there which I needed
so I can get myself together.
Cuz apparently these Ubers stick
together cuz I kept trying to order
another one, but apparently the word got
out that I'm a [\h__\h]
Nobody would come pick me up.
I had to download a whole new app.
I don't know about y'all, but I'm to the
age where I don't like downloading new
apps. I don't like pulling out my credit
card in public and entering the
information. I don't like the two-factor
authenti- I don't like none of that
[\h__\h] I don't want you to I don't want
to go get my glasses so I can let you
know what square the bicycle is in.
I don't want you sending no emails to
the email account I don't [\h__\h] with like
that. I don't want to do none of that.
>> [laughter]
>> I finally did it though.
Did all of that. Downloaded Lyft.
They was like, "Your driver is 1 minute
away." I was like, "Damn, my nigga." I
walked outside. It was the same goddamn
guy.
>> [laughter]
>> He drive for both companies. I was like,
"Ain't that just a bitch?"
I had to apologize.
>> [laughter]
>> Steve?
Oh.
Looks like your sister lives in a really
nice neighborhood. [laughter]